Rinoa approaches Squall across the ballroom and takes his hand, pulling him toward the dance floor.
Rinoa leads Squall onto the floor. He's stiff and reluctant; she coaxes him gently with a smile.
Squall stumbles awkwardly through the first steps as Rinoa guides him across the floor.
Squall misses steps and treads on Rinoa's feet. She smiles patiently as they move together.
Squall finds his rhythm. His movements become less hesitant as they begin to synchronize.
They move together in growing harmony, Rinoa's white dress swirling as they sweep across the floor.
The dance becomes graceful and sweeping. Stars become visible through the open ceiling above them.
Rinoa smiles radiantly at Squall. Shooting stars streak across the sky visible above the ballroom.
They spin in a final elegant rotation as the waltz reaches its peak.
The music fades. Squall and Rinoa stand together under the open ceiling showing a starfield, other dancers around them. The dance is over.